Schaefer, Vincent; Papers ua902.010
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus, 1891-1993; 1; 21.0 cubic ft.
  - Correspondence, 1939-1954; Undated; 1.5
    - Howell, W.E. to K.H. Brown at State House, Albany NY, 1953 April 08 (Box 17 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 77)
    - Hubert, Ernest, 1948 August 31-1949 December 05 (Box 17 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 78)
    - Hurd, Dorothy to Schaefer- Re: Wyoming, 1946 November-1948 January (Box 17 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 79)
    - Icing Research: Rime on Mount Washington, 1945 November 26 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
    - Industrial Museum for General Electric, 1931 November 27; 1931 December 02 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
    - Jet Stream and Cloud-related Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
    - Jet Stream and Cloud-related Correspondence with Additional News Clips and Research Notes, 1954 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
    - Jet Stream, Clouds and Sweden- W.E. Hubert, 1952 December 02 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
    - Jordan, J.P (Syracuse Works) and K. Blodgett, 1948 August-1948 September (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
    - Journal of Colloid Science and K. Blodgett, 1946 September-1947 September (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
    - Langmuir, I. and Dorothy Wrinch (Smith College), 1947 October-1947 November (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
    - Langmuir, I. and the Government of the Province of Alberta Dept. of Agriculture- Field Crops Branch, 1945 February; 1945 October; 1947 February (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 9)
    - Langmuir, I. and J.L. Kavanau, 1947 February 27; 1947 March 03 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 10)
    - Langmuir, I. Letters- General, 1950; 1951 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 11)
    - Langmuir, I.- Protein Monolayers, 1939 August 11 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 12)
    - Langmuir, I to Margaret Bakuzonis from Socorro, New Mexico, 1953 April 22 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 13)
    - Langmuir, I. to Schaefer from Arizona, 1953 May 01 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 14)
    - Letters about Schaefer, 1941; 1947 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 15)
    - Linear Expansion of Rails, Milton Jay Kimmel, 1952 April 25 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 16)
    - Liquid Lens Press Release with Photograph, 1953 February 24 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 17)
    - "Ludox" Colloidal Silica, DuPont, 1949 June 01 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 18)
    - McKibben, Dr. J.L. (Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory) and K. Blodgett- Electrostatic Accelerators, 1948 February; 1948 March; 1948 July (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 19)
    - Meteorite Specimens, Smithsonian Institution, 1943 September 18 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 20)
    - Milliken and Farwell, Inc. to Schaefer and Langmuir, 1947 June-1947 August (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 21)
    - Morgan McDermott Post No.7, Tucson, AZ, 1947 April-1948 April (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 22)
    - Mott, Harvey (Phoenix Republic) and Amos Hoff (Phoenix Junior College) to and from V. Schaefer and I. Langmuir, 1947 July-1948 January (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 23)
    - Multicell Systems- from G.E. Apparatus Dept., 1951 November 02 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 24)
    - Nakaya, U- Travel to Oslo and Need for Movie Film (Includes Photo of Anaya Family), 1948 June; 1949 September; Undated (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 25)
    - National Military Establishment- Research and Development Board, 1948 July-1948 August; 1949 April (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 26)
    - Natural History- Proposed Photo Series (Includes Images with Schaefer's Captions, 1943 May 25 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
    - Naval Research Lab to I. Langmuir- Personnel Evaluation, 1948 May 07 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 28)
    - Navy Department Office of Naval Research, 1952 July 03 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 29)
    - North American Weather Consultants, Santa Barbara Municipal Airport, 1952 June 27 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 30)
    - Office of Secretary of Defense, 1954 February 05 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
    - Paschkis, Victor to General Electric, with reply, 1947 February (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 32)
    - Philo, Alice Warner to Schaefer, 1947 February 02 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 33)
    - Postcard from Paris, 1952 August 03 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 34)
    - Proposal for Support by the Office of Naval Research- Post Project Cirrus (with follow-up letter), 1952 April 21; 1952 May 05 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 35)
    - Revised Proposal to Office of Naval Research for Past Project Cirrus Work, 1952 May 27 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 36)
    - Rice, Maurice to Dr. Irving Langmuir- Description of Weather Event, with Pictures, 1950 February 09 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 37)
    - Roan, Kathleen to V. Schaefer, 1948 May 23; 1948 June 04; 1948 June 10 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 38)
    - Robbins Motion Picture Service, 1949 March 25; 1949 April 20 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 39)
    - Shade, David/Apex Tool Company to K. Blodgett, with reply, 1947 July-1947 August (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 40)
    - Split Rock Lodge- Snow for Ski Facilities, 1946 December-1948 January (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 41)
    - State University of New York to I. Langmuir- Langmuir's Resignation from Board of Trustees, 1949 September 12 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 42)
    - Stetson, Harlan T.- Letter re: Mean Hourly Discharge, 1944 May 02 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 43)
    - Surface Replicas: Biological Applications, 1942 October 10 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 44)
    - Surface Replicas: Botanical Applications, Undated (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 45)
    - Teale, Edwin Way- Letter to Schaefer (Snowflakes), 1945 August 12 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 46)
    - Union of South Africa- Scientific Liaison Office, 1947 March-1948 January (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 47)
    - Vancouver Forest Service, 1947 November-1948 July (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 48)
    - Ventilation Studies, 1947 January 21 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 49)
    - Vonnegut, B. to I. Langmuir- Rain Gauge Cloth (Cloth Included), 1944 August 01 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 50)
    - Walton, Sande, High School Student, to I. Langmuir, with reply, 1974 September 22; 1947 October 14 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 51)
    - Waugh, Dr. David to I. Langmuir and K. Blodgett, 1947 February-1947 April (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 52)
    - Waugh, Dr. David (MIT) from I. Langmuir, 1948 April 30 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 53)
    - Weather Control: Article for Grolier, 1951 June-1951 July (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 54)
    - Wood, R.W., 1942 September 14 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 55)
    - Wrinch, Dr. Dorothy- Oxford University, Undated (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 56)
    - Yagoda, H. Article and Letter to Schaefer: "Analytical Patterns in the Study of Mineral and Biological Materials", 1943 February; 1944 April 29 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 57)
    - Younger, Dorothy- Rhyming Letter, 1946 November 28 (Box 18 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 58)
  - Subject Files, 1891-1978; Undated; 1.6
    The Schaefer subject files are a collection of brochures, notes, and other ephemera that have enduring value but do not belong in other categories such as cloud seeding or snow and ice research. These files include research notes from sources other than General Electric; scientists and entrepreneurs frequently exchanged results of their work with one another, but to avoid confusion, the work of Schaefer and other G.E. scientists can be found in the next subseries while informal research notes and observations by others are located here.
    - Address Book, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 1)
    - Aerial Photos, Assorted, 1942 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 2)
    - Aeronautical Chart for Hudson, 1947 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 3)
    - Air Material Command, Dayton Ohio- Temperature Distribution notes and photos, ca. 1946 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 4)
    - Advancing and Receding Contact- Angles, 1949-1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 5)
    - Albany Airport Instrument Approach Chart, 1951 October 04 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 6)
    - Amateur Weathering of America, 1947 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 7)
    - American Chemical Society, Eastern New York Section, Directory and By-Laws, 1949 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 8)
    - American Chemical Society- Schaefer's Enrollment for 1938, 1937 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 9)
    - American Geophysical Union- Relationship with General Electric, 1945-1946; 1948; 1952 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 10)
    - American Men of Science Questionnaire, ca. 1948 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 11)
    - American Meteorological Society Committee on Professional Ethics and Standards-Report to the Council, 1951 May 03 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 12)
    - American Meteorological Society, Meetings and Code of Ethics, 1949-1951 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 13)
    - American Meteorological Society, Meeting Programs, 1946-1954; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 14)
    - American Polar Society- Membership Invitation, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 15)
    - American Society for Testing Materials- Poster Advertising V.J. Schaefer and P.E. Kraght Speaking Engagement, 1948 April 13 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
    - Apprenticeship Records, 1923-1924 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 16)
    - Atmospheric Data from Rocket-Flights- News article and letter, 1948; 1949 January 13 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 17)
    - Atmospheric Motion and Particle Movement, 1953 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 18)
    - Biography- Bensin, Basil M., 1948 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 19)
    - Binaural Effect Studies, 1942 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 20)
    - Biography of Schaefer, Capital Cogs, 1950 September 06 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 21)
    - Biography of Schaefer, Manuscript, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 22)
    - Bishops Cap (Mitella sp.) photo negative, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 23)
    - News Clipping, Award Recipient (photocopy)- Blodgett, Katherine, 1972 November 09 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 24)
    - Boeing Aircraft Photos, 1960; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 25)
    - Brazilian Traction, Light and Power 36th Annual Report, 1948 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 26)
    - British Glaciological Society, 1947-1951 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 27)
    - Calgon- Formulas, Properties, Graphs, 1937; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 28)
    - Calrod Experiment Summary with Letter, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 29)
    - Candid Camera- Picture of I. Langmuir, 1944 December 29 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 30)
    - Cartoons and Comics, 1947-1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 31)
    - Centennial Publication: "G.E. 100-Toward the Second Century", 1978 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 32)
    - Character Reference for Schaefer, 1947 September 16 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 33)
    - "Class Assignment" Notebook, 1934-1935 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 34)
    - Climatic Trends in the Northeastern U.S. Symposium, 1952 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 35)
    - "Cloud Forms of the Jet Stream" articles with related photos & news clippings, 1953 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 36)
    - Cold Chamber: Bowser, Inc. Refrigeration Division Brochure- Temperature Altitude and Humidity Simulation Units, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 37)
    - Cold Chamber: Demonstration at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 38)
    - Colloid Symposium (MIT)- Program of Papers, 1938 June 09-1968 June 11 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 39)
    - Committee on Geophysical Science of the joint Research and Development Board- Panel on Meteorology, 1947 April 23 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 40)
    - Compendium of Meteorology tentative table of contents with partial letter, 1949 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 41)
    - Costs for Making Copies of Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 42)
    - Crystallization of Metals, Rocks and Ice-Symposium, 1951 October (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 43)
    - Current Science, Vol. XXVIII #4, featuring I. Langmuir, V. Schaefer, K. Blodgett, C.G. Suits, 1942 October 05-1942 October 09 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 44)
    - Distribution of Contract recommendation (with note to Schaefer from "Vic", Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 45)
    - Dutch (?) Meteorological Map, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 46)
    - Eastern Snow Conference Materials, 1950 February 16-1950 February 17; 1951 February 15-1951 February 17; 1952 February 14-1952 February 15 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 47)
    - Edison General Electric Company: Instructions to Foremen Fragile Item, 1891 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 48)
    - Einladung zur Sitzung der Naturforschenden Gesellschaft- Zurich, 1953 December (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 49)
    - Electron Microscopy: Description with Letter, 1942 June 02; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 50)
    - Electron Microscopy: Newspaper Clippings, 1941 November 06; 1941 November 21 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 51)
    - Electron Microscopy: Symposium, 1942 November 27 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 52)
    - Electronic Stratometer vs. Radio Sonde- Nomenclature Change from Minutes of University of Chicago Dept. of Meteorology, 1945 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 53)
    - Employee Rating Sheets instructions, 1949 July (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 54)
    - "Essais de Modification des Nuages dans les Pyrenees", 1951 June 06 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 55)
    - Fasciation (collected articles on), 1948; 1971; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 56)
    - Fire Danger Meter and Burning Index Meter, 1942 April (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 57)
    - Fires in Ontario- Map and Data, 1948 June (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 58)
    - "A Five- Year Record of Lightning Storms and Forest Fires", H.T. Gisborne, 1931 April (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 59)
    - Flashtubes- General Electric and Strobo Research, 1947-1948; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 60)
    - Copy of 1752 letter on Electricity- Franklin, Benjamin, 1920 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 61)
    - General Engineering Lab Research Publications, 1955-1959 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 62)
    - Geodimeter description, 1951 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 63)
    - Groundwater Elevation in the Hudson- Mohawk Drainage Basin, 1931-1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 64)
    - Hailstones, 1949-1950; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 65)
    - High Altitude Observatory: Contributions and Supplemental Information, 1953 March (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 66)
    - High Voltage Radiography Symposium, 1952 March 04-1952 March 05 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 67)
    - Identification badge- Schaefer, General Electric, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 68)
    - Incense (Blue Smoke) graph, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 69)
    - Institute of Navigation Meeting Program, 1947 February 13-1947 February 14 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 70)
    - Instructions for Operating the Kodaslide Projector, Model 2A, ca. 1947 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 71)
    - Instructions: Portable and Switchboard Recording Instruments (Types CF-1, 2, 4, and 5), ca. 1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 72)
    - Instrumentation for Industrial Hygiene Symposium, 1954 May 24-1954 May 27 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 73)
    - Iodine Abstracts and Reviews, Vol. I #3-6 and Vol. II #1, 1950 January-1950 October; 1951 January-1951 April (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 74)
    - Isotopes-Supplement #1, 1949 September (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 75)
    - Japanese Article, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 76)
    - Jet Stream- Radio press releases, 1953 January 26 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 77)
    - Laboratory Conference No.8- research presentations, artists rendering at the knolls, plans for research lab, 1945 October 11-1945 October 12 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 78)
    - Laboratory Study and Development Program, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 79)
    - Landform Map of the Northwestern States, Copyright 1941, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 80)
    - Landform Map of the United States, 1939 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 81)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Biography by A.C. Langmuir, 1932 December (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 82)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Biography by K.B. Blodgett, 1933 July (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 83)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Biography by W.R. Whitney, 1941 February (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 84)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Biography Reprinted from Scientific American, 1937 September (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 85)
    - Langmuir, Irving: "Book U" Supplements, 1952-1953 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 86)
    - Langmuir, Irving: The Collected Works of Irving Langmuir-Introduction to Volume VII by Schaefer, 1960 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 87)
    - Langmuir, Irving: The Collected Works of Irving Langmuir-Introduction to Volume 10 by Schaefer, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 88)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Columbia University Engineering Center News, 1951 December (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 89)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Memorial Speech by Nephews, Union College, 1957 August 21 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 90)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Memorials by Schaefer, 1957-1958 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 91)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Perkin Medal Award, 1928 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 92)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Photo album index, ca. 1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 93)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Portrait Photos, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 94)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Portrait Photo, Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Priestley Medal Award, 1929 October (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 95)
    - Langmuir, Irving: Publications list, Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 96)
    - Langmuir, Irving: "A Tribute to Irving Langmuir, 1881-1957", 1957 August 19 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 97)
    - Le Recueil, 1947 March (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 98)
    - "Lichtstreuung an Aerosolteilchen", 1952 April (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 99)
    - Map: United States Department of Agriculture Forest Service, 1948 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 100)
    - Memo: H.T. Gisborne- Use of B-29 Jets in Lightning Fire Prevention, 1949 June 29 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 101)
    - Meteorological office equipment requirements, 1952 March 06 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 102)
    - Mohawk Association of Scientists and Engineers Newsletter, 1952 August 27 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 103)
    - Mohawk Association of Scientists and Engineers Newsletter (MASE), 1953 June 17 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 104)
    - Multicell structure- official patent with original letter regarding application of invention, 1950 November 03; 1956 January 24 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 105)
    - Museum Service-Bulletin of Rochester Museum of Arts & Sciences, 1939 March; 1939 April (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 106)
    - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics- Research abstracts, 1951 June 15 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 107)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1939-1950; Undated (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 108)
    - New Mexico Institute of Mining and Technology Catalog, 1951-1952 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 109)
    - New York Academy of Sciences Meetings, 1949- 1950 (Box 19 (1-General Electric- Non-Project Cirrus), Folder 110)